Hello everyone, in this video, we will learn how to use the PBR sticker generator.
First, upload a sticker to the costume.
You will see that the selected picture has been added as a sticker text.
All other stickers are empty.
Let's create a hair line sticker first.
Click on the PBR sticker generator button on the right side of the hair line sticker menu.
It will automatically create a hair line sticker based on the texture.
You can adjust the intensity value to adjust the sticker effect.
Click on the PBR sticker generator button next to the summoning picture to create a summoning picture in the same way.
Click on the Browse button, you will see that the created sticker is stored in AppData.
Continue to create a transparent picture.
To create a rough texture, you can set the surface rough texture option to Sticker, then click on the PBR sticker generator button.
Click on the checkbox to view names.
Next, select one of the 3 color Global inside the race.
eBay campaign Kuoy is going to be launched.
On the first download page very specifically,
you can buy info based on the surcharge on the goal that you have used in the algorithm.
Click on the PBR sticker on the bottom left channel.
Click on the Merc assigned image selection bar.
Click on Done.
Adjust the intensity value to create the appropriate material effect
This function can be used to create PBR stickers for fabric, buttons, eyes, stickers, adhesives, lines, and smudgers
The above is the introduction of the PBR sticker generator
Thank you for watching, see you in the next video